panopticsearch.com 2008-05-09

# Funnelback - Internet and Enterprise Search - Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy 

Personal information collected by Funnelback is treated as confidential and is protected by the Australian Privacy Act 1988. Personal information is information relating to an individual whose identity is apparent, or can reasonably be ascertained, from the information or opinion provided.

#### Site visit data

This site is operated by Funnelback with the use of an external service provider. When visiting this site, a record of your visit is logged. The following information is recorded for statistical purposes and is used by Funnelback to help improve the site. The following information is supplied by your browser:

  * the user's server address
  * the user's operating system (for example Windows, Mac etc)
  * the user's top level domain name (for example .com, .gov, .au, .uk etc)
  * the date and time of the visit to the site
  * the pages accessed and the documents downloaded
  * the previous site visited
  * the type of browser used.

No attempt will be made to identify users or their browsing activities except in the unlikely event of an investigation, where a law enforcement agency may exercise a warrant to inspect the internet service provider's logs.

#### Collection of personal information

When you e-mail us: 

  * we will record your e-mail address
  * we will only use your e-mail address for the purpose for which you provided it
  * we will not disclose it without your consent except where Funnelback may be required by law to disclose certain information.

Should you decide to use an online form, such as the Funnelback quote request form: 

  * we will record your name, e-mail address, address, telephone number, and other information as requested.
  * we will only use this information for the purpose for which you provided it
  * we will not disclose this information without your consent except where Funnelback may be required by law to disclose certain information.

We will, at your request, provide you with access to any information which we have collected about you through this website in accordance with Information Privacy Principle 6, Privacy Act 1988 (Cth). To gain access to this information you should contact us (see details below). If you believe that any information is inaccurate, incomplete or out of date, please contact us and we will revise the relevant information in accordance with Information Privacy Principle 7, Privacy Act 1988 (Cth).

#### Cookies

A cookie is a text string that is included with Hypertext Transfer Protocol (HTTP) requests and responses. Cookies are used to maintain state information as you navigate different pages on a web site or return to the web site at a later time. Cookies cannot be used to execute code (run programs) or deliver viruses to your computer.

#### Persistent vs. session cookies

Cookies are either stored in memory (session cookies) or placed on your hard disk (persistent cookies).

#### How to access cookies settings in your browser

You have the ability to enable or disable cookies, or have Internet Explorer or Netscape prompt you before accepting cookies. Note that disabling cookies may prevent some web services from working correctly, and disabling cookies does not make you anonymous or prevent web sites from tracking your browsing habits. HTTP requests still include information about where you came from (HTTP Referer), your IP address, browser version, operating system, and other information (see Site Visit Data above).

#### Internet Explorer

1\. In Internet Explorer, click Internet Options on the Tools menu, and then click the Security tab.  
2\. Click the Web content zone you want, and then click Custom Level.  
3\. Under Cookies , click the options you want, click OK , and then click OK.

#### Netscape

1\. From the Edit menu, choose Preferences.  
2\. Click the Advanced category.  
3\. Click one of the radio buttons in the Cookies section. Important: In most cases, "Accept all cookies" is the best choice. The second button means that your computer will not send a cookie to a server that did not originate it.  
4\. If you want to be notified when Communicator accepts a cookie, check "Warn me before accepting a cookie."

#### Security of information

Your personal information will not be released unless the law requires or permits it or your permission is given. We provide a secure environment and a reliable system but you should be aware that there may be inherent risks associated with the transmission of information via the Internet. For those who do not wish to use the Internet, Funnelback provides alternative ways of obtaining and providing information.

#### Who to contact

To contact Funnelback about privacy matters, please use the details provided on the 'contact us' page.
